const data = [
    {
        question: "Identify the infinite loop.",
        options: ["for(;;)","for(int i=0; i<1; i--)","for(int i=0; ; i++)","All of above"],
        correct_option: "All of above"
    },
    {
        question: "What is Runnable?",
        options: ["Abstract class","Interface","Class","Method"],
        correct_option: "Interface"
    },
    {
        question: "Exception created by try block is caught in which block",
        options: ["catch","throw","final","None of these"],
        correct_option: "catch"
    },
    {
        question: "Where is System class defined?",
        options: ["java.lang.package","java.util.package","java.io.package","None"],
        correct_option: "java.lang.package"
    },
    {
        question: "When an array is passed to a method, what does the method receive?",
        options: ["Reference of array","Copy of array","Length of the array","Copy of first element"],
        correct_option: "Reference of array"
    },
    {
        question: "When is the object created with new keyword?",
        options: ["At run time","At compile time","Depend upon code","None"],
        correct_option: "At run time"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the size of float and double in java?",
        options: ["32 and 64","32 and 32","64 and 64","None"],
        correct_option: "32 and 64"
    },
    {
        question: "Output of Math.floor(3.6)?",
        options: ["3","3.0","4","4.0"],
        correct_option: "3.0"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the implicit return type of constructor?",
        options: ["No return type","A class object in which it is defined","void","None"],
        correct_option: "A class object in which it is defined"
    },
    {
        question: "When is the finalize() method called?",
        options: ["Before garbage collection","Before an object goes out of scope","Before a variable goes out of scope","None"],
        correct_option: "Before garbage collection"
    }
];
export default data;